Yale Peabody Museum Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
Yale Peabody Museum Archives
1968-1982
YPMAR.000056
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
10
several rooms/offices
Archives of the Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History.
Archives, Yale Peabody Museum
Biographical Sketch
The Peabody Museum of Natural History at Yale University has an extensive and rich archive of materials related not only to the history of the Museum, the individuals involved in its founding, and the early days of its collections, but also to the early history of higher education in the natural sciences in the United States, especially in paleontology. Much of the Yale Peabody Museum's exceptional collections of over 12 million specimens and objects in anthropology, zoology, paleontology, entomology, ornithology, geology, mineralogy, meteorites and historical scientific instruments have been photographically documented.
Description of the Material
The archives of the Yale Peabody Museum contain material relating to the founding and history of the Museum as well as the archives various faculty, staff and affiliates.
35mm slides; Paintings; Documents; Maps; Yale Peabody Museum; Yale University
- George Wieland archives
  Scope and Contents
  Material pertaining to George Wieland including field notebooks, ledgers, correspondence, and photographs
  - Notebooks., 000909
    - Field notebook., 1898 - 1901; 000915
    - Field notebook., Jun - Oct 1902; 000916
    - Notebook. Record of photomicrographs, new series., 17 Nov 1908; 000910
    - Notebook. University of Wyoming, USN, and Colorado cycad section list, 1899; 000913
    - Notebook. Cycadeoidea trunk list. Copied by T. A. Bostwick. Black Hills list plus., Jan 1915; 000912
    - Notebook. Notes on the Fossil Cycads of the Yale Museum, George Wieland. Includes list of Yale types., Nov 1898; 000911
    - Notebook. Cycadeoid and other, Trial and type sections, all. Cut by Wieland beginning December 1, 1898., 000914
  - Photographs and sketches., 000941
    - Photograph. Wieland with Ross R. Wolfe posing behind three fossil cycadeoids in Stephenville, TX., 13 Jan 1937; 000958
    - Photograph. Wieland at Turtle Horizon, Cycad Monument, 1927; 000947
    - Photograph. Wieland in Field. ProbablyTurtle Horizon, Cycad Monument., 1927; 000948
    - Photograph. Marties(?) Hill from Cycad Monument, 5 Aug 1927; 000949
    - Photograph. Wieland in his home next to fireplace., 000942
    - Photograph. Wieland in the field, 000943
    - Photograph. Wieland at excavation site with field crew., 000944
    - Photograph. Wieland in the field. Probably at Turtle Horizon, Cycad Monument., 000946
    - Photograph. Wieland in the field. Probably at Turtle Horizon, Cycad Monument., 000950
    - Photograph. Wieland pointing out view of north boundary of Fossil Cycad National Monument, 000951
    - Photograph. Portrait of George R. Wieland., 000952
    - Photograph. Wieland posing with mounted Archelon skeleton., 000953
    - Photograph. Sketch of cycadeoid., 000954
    - Photograph. Images of male and female cycadeoid., 000956
    - Photograph. Wieland posing with group of women around a fossil cycadeoid., 000957
    - Photograph. Wieland posing with faculty members from John Tarleton College: Prof. Scott, Hugh M. Smith, Ross R. Wolfe, and Davis in from on three fossil cycadeoids., 000959
    - Photograph. Three fossil cycadeoids., 000960
    - Photograph. Three fossil cycadeoids., 000961
    - Photograph. Wieland in the field. L. South West. Exc.A.1, 000962
    - Photograph. Looking South East over C. superba excavation (above faulting), 000963
    - Photograph. Looking North east. Quarry III, V, VI. Quarry I in foreground., 000964
    - Photograph. Looking West. Quarry VI, V, III., 000965
    - Photograph. Wieland in the field with fossil cycadeoid., 000966
    - Photograph. Fossil cycadeoid next to modern cycads in garden., 000967
    - Photograph. Looking east. Quarries V, VI., 000968
    - Sketch. Diagramatic sketch of Cycadeoidea dacotensis. Includes images of front and back side of paper., 000945
    - Sketch. Cross section of cycadeoid with number and letter labels., 000955
- Stanley N. Botwinik Slide Collection, 1968-1982; Series I
  35mm slide collection of Stanley Botwinik.
  - Africa., 000064
    - Samburu warriors. Kenya, Samburu. Sep 1968., 000100
    - Samburu woman. Kenya, Samburu. Sep 1968., 000101
    - Turkana chief. Kenya, Lake Rudolph. Sep 1968., 000102
    - Cheetah mother and cubs at kill. Tanzania, Serengeti. Sep 1968., 000103
    - Lion cubs. Kenya, Keekorok. Oct 1970., 000118
    - Lion. Tanzania, Serengeti. Oct 1970., 000119
    - Hippo mother and child. Uganda, Victoria Nile. Oct 1970., 000120
    - Hippo mother and child. Uganda, Victoria Nile. Oct 1970., 000121
    - Hippo mother and child. Uganda, Victoria Nile. Oct 1970., 000122
    - Cheetah. Tanzania, Serengeti. Oct 1970., 000123
    - Elephant mother and child. Uganda, Chobe. Oct 1970., 000124
    - White Fronted Bee Eater. Uganda, Victoria Nile. Oct 1970., 000125
    - Male Impala. Tanzania, Lake Manyara. Oct 1970., 000126
    - Crocodile. Uganda, Victoria Nile. Oct 1970., 000127
    - Elephant. Tanzania, Lake Manyara. Oct 1970., 000128
    - Burchell's zebra. Kenya (East Africa). Oct 1970., 000129
    - Leopard portrait. Tanzania, Serengeti. Oct 1970., 000130
    - Zebra. Botswana. Sep 1971., 000131
    - White-bellied bustard. Kenya, Masai Mara. Sep 1973., 000173
    - Hooded vulture. Kenya, Masai Mara. Sep 1973., 000174
    - Lilac-breasted roller. Kenya, Masai Mara. Sep 1973., 000175
    - Secretary bird. Kenya, Masai Mara. Sep 1973., 000176
    - Saddle-bill stork. Kenya, Masai Mara. Sep 1973., 000177
    - Saddle-bill stork. Kenya, Masai Mara. Sep 1973., 000178
    - Bohor reedbuck (male). Kenya, Masai Mara. Sep 1973., 000179
    - Bohor reedbuck (female). Kenya, Masai Mara. Sep 1973., 000180
    - Lioness and cub. Kenya, Masai Mara. Sep 1973., 000181
    - Lion cub. Kenya, Masai Mara. Sep 1973., 000182
    - Sunset. Kenya, Masai Mara. Sep 1973., 000183
    - Hooded vulture. Kenya, Masai Mara. Sep 1973., 000184
    - Egyptian goose. Kenya, M.K.S.C. Sep 1973., 000185
    - Sacred ibis. Kenya, M.K.S.C. Sep 1973., 000186
    - Crowned crane. Kenya, M.K.S.C. Sep 1973., 000187
    - Egyptian goose. Kenya, M.K.S.C. Sep 1973., 000188
    - White pelican. Kenya, M.K.S.C. Sep 1973., 000189
    - Koro Koro. Kenya, Sankuri. Sep 1973., 000190
    - Koro Koro. Kenya, Sankuri. Sep 1973., 000191
    - Cape Rook. Kenya, Samburu. Sep 1973., 000192
    - Vulturine guinea fowl. Kenya, Samburu. Sep 1973., 000193
    - Sunrise. Tanzania, Serengeti camp. Sep 1973., 000194
    - Olive baboon (young). Tanzania, Lake Manyara. Sep 1973., 000195
    - Olive baboon and baby. Tanzania, Lake Manyara. Sep 1973., 000196
    - Goliath heron. Kenya, Lake Naivasha. Sep 1973., 000197
    - Cheetah with kill. Kenya, Amboseli. Sep 1973., 000198
    - Sunset and game. Kenya, Amboseli. Sep 1973., 000199
    - Red and yellow barbet. Kenya, Nairobi. Sep 1973., 000200
    - Burchell's zebra. Kenya, Nairobi. Sep 1973., 000201
    - Tsavo West. Kenya, Tsavo West. Oct 1973., 000202
    - Tsavo West. Kenya, Tsavo West. Oct 1973., 000203
    - Lion pride. Kenya, Tsavo West. Oct 1973., 000204
    - Lion pride. Kenya, Tsavo West. Oct 1973., 000205
    - Elephant. Tanzania (East Africa). Sep 1970., 000497
    - Reticulated giraffe. Kenya, Samburu. Oct 1970., 000498
    - Burchell's zebra. Kenya, Nairobi Pk. Oct 1970., 000499
    - Rhino. Kenya, Tsavo. Oct 1970., 000500
    - Crowned crane. Kenya, Mt. Kenya Safari Club. Oct 1970., 000501
    - Lions mating. Tanzania, North Crater. Sep 1973., 000516
    - Black swan. Kenya, M.K.S.C. Sep 1973., 000517
    - Black swan. Kenya, M.K.S.C. Sep 1973., 000518
    - Crowned crane. Kenya, M.K.S.C. Sep 1973., 000519
    - Crowned crane. Kenya (East Africa). Sep 1973., 000520
    - Crowned crane. Kenya, M.K.S.C. Sep 1973., 000521
    - Crowned crane. Kenya, M.K.S.C. Sep 1973., 000522
    - Sunrise. Tanzania, Serengeti. Sep 1973., 000523
    - Sunrise. Tanzania, Serengeti. Sep 1973., 000524
  - Antarctica., 000066
    - Humpback whale. Antarctica, Paradise Bay. Feb 1972., 000132
    - Humpback whale. Antarctica, Paradise Bay. Feb 1972., 000133
    - Adelie penguins feeding. Antarctica, Port Lockroy. Feb 1972., 000134
    - Adelie penguins. Antarctica, Port Lockroy. Feb 1972., 000135
    - Elephant seal. Antarctica, Potter Cove. Feb 1972., 000136
    - Elephant seal. Antarctica, Potter Cove. Feb 1972., 000137
    - Crabeater seals. Antarctica, Paradise Bay. Feb 1972., 000138
    - Crabeater seal. Antarctica, Paradise Bay. Feb 1972., 000139
    - Weddell seal. Antarctica, Paradise Bay. Feb 1972., 000140
    - Weddell seal. Antarctica, Paradise Bay. Feb 1972., 000141
    - Elephant seals. Antarctica, Potter Cove. Feb 1972., 000142
    - Elephant seal. Antarctica, Potter Cove. Feb 1972., 000143
    - Elephant seals. Antarctica, Potter Cove. Feb 1972., 000144
    - Tabular iceberg at sea. Antarctica. Feb 1972., 000145
    - Pintado petrel. Antarctica, Paradise Bay. Feb 1972., 000146
    - Pintado petrel. Antarctica, Paradise Bay. Feb 1972., 000147
    - Wilson's Storm petrels (at sea). Antarctica. Feb 1972., 000148
    - Ice Pack. Antarctica. Feb 1972., 000149
    - Ice Pack. Antarctica. Feb 1972., 000150
    - Giant petrels at sea, feeding. Antarctica. Feb 1972., 000151
    - The Drake Passage. Antarctica. Feb 1972., 000152
    - Adelie penguins. Antarctica, Port Lockroy. Feb 1972., 000153
    - Chinstrap penguin rookery. Antarctica, Deception Island. Feb 1974., 000212
    - Iceberg. Antarctica, Hope Bay. Feb 1974., 000213
    - Adelie penguin. Antarctica, Esperanza Station. Feb 1974., 000214
    - Chinstrap penguin. Antarctica, Paradise Bay. Feb 1974., 000215
    - Ice pack. Antarctica. Feb 1972., 000503
    - Gentoo penguin. Antarctica, Paradise Bay. Feb 1972., 000504
    - Gentoo penguin and chick. Antarctica, Paradise Bay. Feb 1972., 000505
    - Gentoo penguin feeding chick. Antarctica, Paradise Bay. Feb 1972., 000506
    - Gentoo penguin and chicks. Antarctica, Paradise Bay. Feb 1972., 000507
    - Crabeater seal. Antarctica, Paradise Bay. Feb 1972., 000508
    - Crabeater seal. Antarctica, Paradise Bay. Feb 1972., 000509
  - Bonaire., 000060
    - Tube sponges. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000436
    - Tube sponges. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000437
    - Vase sponge. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000438
    - Queen angelfish. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000439
    - Crinoid. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000440
    - Crinoid. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000441
    - Crinoid. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000442
    - Arrow crab. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000443
    - Arrow crab. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000444
    - Nassau Grouper. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000445
    - Vase sponge. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000446
    - Honeycomb cowfish. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000447
    - Smooth trunkfish. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000448
    - Smooth trunkfish. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000449
    - Smooth trunkfish. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000450
    - Anemone. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000451
    - Anemone. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000452
    - Anemone. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000453
    - Spotted moray eel. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000454
    - Spotted moray eel. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000455
    - Spotted moray eel. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000456
    - Spotted moray eel. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000457
    - Spotted moray eel. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000458
    - Spotted moray eel. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000459
    - Plume worms. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000460
    - Lizardfish. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000461
    - Peterson shrimp. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000462
    - Peterson shrimp. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000463
    - Peterson shrimp. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. Aug 1980., 000464
    - Queen angelfishes. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. May 1982., 000487
    - French angelfish. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. May 1982., 000488
    - Anemone and shrimp. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. May 1982., 000489
    - Anemone and shrimp. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. May 1982., 000490
    - Rock beauty. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. May 1982., 000491
    - Rock beauty. Netherlands Antilles, Bonaire. May 1982., 000492
  - Brazil., 000062
    - Capybara. Brazil, Amazon River. Nov 1972., 000154
    - Matamath. Brazil, Amazon River. Nov 1972., 000155
    - Tapir. Brazil, Amazon River. Nov 1972., 000156
    - Python. Brazil, Amazon River. Nov 1972., 000157
    - Python. Brazil, Amazon River. Nov 1972., 000158
    - Piranha. Brazil, Amazon River. Nov 1972., 000159
    - Piranha. Brazil, Amazon River. Nov 1972., 000160
    - Blue and yellow macaw (Ara ararauna). Brazil, Amazon River. Nov 1973., 000206
    - Blue and yellow macaw (Ara ararauna). Brazil, Amazon River. Nov 1973., 000207
    - Red and green macaw. Brazil, Amazon River. Nov 1973., 000208
    - Red and green macaw. Brazil, Amazon River. Nov 1973., 000209
    - Channel-billed toucan. Brazil, Amazon River. Nov 1973., 000210
    - Channel-billed toucan. Brazil, Amazon River. Nov 1973., 000211
  - Florida., 000058
    - Great White Heron. United States, Florida, Everglades. Apr 1973., 000165
    - Blue-stripe grunts. United States, Florida, Islamorada. Dec 1975., 000233
    - Blue-stripe grunts. United States, Florida, Islamorada. Dec 1975., 000234
    - Gray angelfish. United States, Florida, Islamorada. Dec 1975., 000235
    - Horse-eye jack. United States, Florida, Islamorada. May 1976., 000237
    - Queen angelfish. United States, Florida, Islamorada. Oct 1977., 000288
    - Bluestriped grunt. United States, Florida, Islamorada. Oct 1977., 000289
    - Bluestriped grunt. United States, Florida, Islamorada. Oct 1977., 000290
    - Bluestriped grunts. United States, Florida, Islamorada. Oct 1977., 000291
    - Blue tang. United States, Florida, Islamorada. Oct 1977., 000292
  - Galapagos., 000068
    - Galapagos turtle. Papua, New Guinea, Wanigela. Sep 1969., 000108
    - Koala bear. Galapagos, Hood Island. Apr 1970., 000112
    - Blue footed booby (female). Galapagos, Hood Island. Apr 1970., 000113
    - Blue footed Booby (male). Galapagos, Tower Island. Apr 1970., 000114
    - Red footed Booby. Galapagos, Tower Island. Apr 1970., 000115
    - Frigate bird displaying. Galapagos, Tower Island. Apr 1970., 000116
    - Marine iguana. Galapagos, Hood Island. Apr 1970., 000117
    - Marine iguana. Galapagos, Punta Espinoza, Fernandina. Apr 1973., 000161
    - Darwin's finch. Galapagos, near Daphne. Apr 1973., 000162
    - Swallow-tailed gull and chick. Galapagos, Tower Island. Apr 1973., 000163
    - Land iguana. Galapagos, South Plaza Island. Apr 1973., 000164
    - Galapagos albatross. Galapagos, Hood Island. Apr 1973., 000166
    - Land iguana. Galapagos, South Plaza Island. Apr 1973., 000167
    - Red-footed booby. Galapagos, Tower Island. Apr 1973., 000168
    - Swallow-tailed gulls. Galapagos, Tower Island. Apr 1973., 000169
    - Swallow-tailed gull (in flight). Galapagos, South Plaza. Apr 1973., 000170
    - Vermillion flycatcher (male). Galapagos, Academy Bay, Santa Cruz. Apr 1973., 000171
    - Blue-footed booby. Galapagos. Aug 1973., 000172
    - Frigate bird (male). Galapagos, Tower Island. Apr 1973., 000510
    - Blue footed boobies (l: male, r: female). Galapagos, Daphne Island. Apr 1973., 000511
    - Blue footed boobies. Galapagos, Daphne Island. Apr 1973., 000512
    - Fur seal. Galapagos, James Bay, James Island. Apr 1973., 000513
    - Fur seal. Galapagos, James Bay, James Island. Apr 1973., 000514
    - Sally-go lightly crab. Galapagos, Fernandina Island, Punta Espinoza. Apr 1973., 000515
  - Grand Cayman., 000059
    - Rock beauty. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Aug 1975., 000224
    - Octopus. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jun 1976., 000238
    - Trumpet fish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jun 1976., 000239
    - Stone crab. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jun 1976., 000240
    - Octopus. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jun 1976., 000241
    - Octopus. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jun 1976., 000242
    - Octopus. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jun 1976., 000243
    - Octopus. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jun 1976., 000244
    - Octopus. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jun 1976., 000245
    - Stonefish (Scorpion fish). British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1976., 000246
    - Urchin and stonefish (scorpion fish). British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1976., 000247
    - Octopus. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul-Aug 1976., 000248
    - Queen parrot fish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul-Aug 1976., 000249
    - Squirrel fish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul-Aug 1976., 000250
    - Blackbar soldierfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul-Aug 1976., 000251
    - Goldspotted eel. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul-Aug 1976., 000252
    - Octopus. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul-Aug 1976., 000253
    - Octopus. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul-Aug 1976., 000254
    - Octopus and sea urchin. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul-Aug 1976., 000255
    - French angelfishes. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul-Aug 1976., 000256
    - Barracuda. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Nov 1976., 000257
    - Tube sponges. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Nov 1976., 000258
    - Gray angelfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1977., 000261
    - Lobster. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1977., 000262
    - Gray angelfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1977., 000263
    - Balloonfish (Puffer). British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1977., 000264
    - Queen angelfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1977., 000265
    - Nassau grouper. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1977., 000266
    - Gorgonian. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1977., 000267
    - Gorgonian. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1977., 000268
    - Diver in baskets. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1977., 000269
    - Tube sponge. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1977., 000270
    - Tube sponge. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1977., 000271
    - Sponges and fire coral. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1977., 000272
    - Vase sponge. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1977., 000273
    - Tube sponges. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1977., 000274
    - Gorgonian trumpetfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1977., 000275
    - Blue tang. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1977., 000276
    - Octopus. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1977., 000277
    - Finger sponge (c/u). British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1977., 000278
    - Gorgonian and diver. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1977., 000279
    - Sea fan (c/u). British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1977., 000280
    - Smooth trunkfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1977., 000281
    - Sea fan (c/u). British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1977., 000282
    - Trumpetfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1977., 000283
    - Sponge (c/u). British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1977., 000284
    - Sponges. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1977., 000285
    - Crinoids. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1977., 000286
    - Tube sponges. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1977., 000287
    - Tube sponges. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Nov 1977., 000293
    - Barracuda. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Nov 1977., 000294
    - Spanish hogfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Nov 1977., 000295
    - Vase sponge. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Nov 1977., 000296
    - Barracuda. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Nov 1977., 000297
    - Octopus. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Nov 1977., 000298
    - Vase sponge. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Nov 1977., 000299
    - Squirrel fish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Nov 1977., 000300
    - French angelfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1978., 000301
    - Blue parrotfish (nite). British West Indies, Grand Cayman. May 1978., 000302
    - Sponge (closeup). British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000303
    - Arrow crab. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000304
    - Sponges. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000305
    - Plume Worms. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000306
    - Sponge (closeup). British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000307
    - Sponge (closeup). British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000308
    - Green moray eel. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000309
    - Bluestriped grunt. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000310
    - Crinoid. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000311
    - Plume Worms. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000312
    - Purple club-tipped anenome. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000313
    - Finger sponge (close-up). British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000314
    - French angelfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000315
    - Queen angelfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000316
    - Queen angelfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000317
    - Queen angelfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000318
    - French angelfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000319
    - Red hermit crab. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000320
    - Flamingo tongue. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000321
    - Purple club-tipped anenome. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000322
    - Gray angelfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000323
    - Sponge (c/u) and bristle star. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000324
    - Sponge (c/u). British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000325
    - Feather-duster worms. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000326
    - Octopus. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000327
    - Feather-dusters. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000328
    - Feather-duster worms. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000329
    - Pufferfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000330
    - Hermit crab. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000331
    - Feather-duster worms. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000332
    - Crinoid. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Jul 1978., 000333
    - Plume worms. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Sep 1978., 000334
    - Hermit crab. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Sep 1978., 000335
    - Crinoid. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Sep 1978., 000336
    - Basket star. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Sep 1978., 000337
    - Flamingo tongue. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Dec 1978., 000338
    - French angelfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Dec 1978., 000339
    - Basket star. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Dec 1978., 000340
    - Spotted goatfish (nite). British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Dec 1978., 000341
    - Hermit crab. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Dec 1978., 000342
    - Fire coral. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Dec 1978., 000343
    - Trumpet fish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Dec 1978., 000344
    - Plume worms. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Dec 1978., 000345
    - Queen triggerfish. British West Indies, Grand Cayman. Dec 1978., 000346